blogbuildingu.com 2008-12-10

# Marketing Loop’s Privacy Policy

MarketingLoop.com is committed to protecting the privacy of my online visitors. I collect information from online visitors who ask to be on my newsletter mailing list and/or receive periodic email announcements. Anyone who wishes can choose to be removed from my mailing list at any time.

In addition, online visitors who wish to purchase a membership through my Web site must provide their name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card number and expiration date. All credit card transactions occur over a secure connection.

All online visitor data collected by MarketingLoop.com is protected against unauthorized access. I will not sell, trade, or give your personal information to other companies or organizations.

## Children’s Privacy

I do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If I learn that I have personal information on a child under the age of 13, I will delete that information from my systems. MarketingLoop.com encourages parents to go online with their kids. Here are a few tips to help make a child’s online experience safer:

  * Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc.
  * Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate.
  * Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child’s information is treated.
  * Check out the FTC’s site  for more tips on protecting children’s privacy online.

#### Contacting Me

I can be reached by contacting:

MarketingLoop.com
